Guide to the Lee P. Brown Papers, 1954-2013 MS 509
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series XI: Houston Mayor, 1997-2004, 213482
  - Subseries D: Speeches, 230937
    - National Night Out, 2003-08-01; 261624 (Box 64, Folder 107)
    - Mayor's Jazz Brunch, 2003-08-03; 261625 (Box 64, Folder 108)
    - National Night Out Downtown Rally, 2003-08-05; 261626 (Box 64, Folder 109)
    - South Belt - Ellington Chamber of Commerce, 2003-08-13; 261627 (Box 64, Folder 110)
    - Ensemble Theatre Gala, 2003-08-15; 261628 (Box 64, Folder 111)
    - Statue of Ghandi Press Conference, 2003-08-21; 261629 (Box 64, Folder 112)
    - Texas Conference of Black Mayors, 2003-08-21; 261630 (Box 64, Folder 113)
    - Texas Conference of Black Mayors, 2003-08-22; 261631 (Box 64, Folder 114)
    - Houston Works Luncheon, 2003-08-25; 261632 (Box 64, Folder 115)
    - Houston's 167th Birthday, 2003-08-26; 261633 (Box 64, Folder 116)
    - Toyota Center Ribbon Cutting, 2003-09-04; 261634 (Box 64, Folder 117)
    - Luanda Government and Business Leaders, 2003-09-10; 261635 (Box 64, Folder 118)
    - Walvis Bay - Namibia, 2003-09-12; 261636 (Box 64, Folder 119)
    - NAACP Annual Banquet - Pine Bluff, AR, 2003-11-01; 261637 (Box 64, Folder 120)
    - Ministers Breakfast, 2003-11; 261638 (Box 64, Folder 121)
    - Houston Area Urban League, 2003-12-19; 261639 (Box 64, Folder 122)
    - The Ensemble Theatre Mortgage Burning Ceremony, 2004-01-01; 261640 (Box 64, Folder 123)
    - METROrail Opening Day, 2004-01-01; 261641 (Box 64, Folder 124)
    - Today Show Appearance, 2004-01-02; 261642 (Box 64, Folder 125)
  - Subseries E: Travel, 230938
    - Travel Index, 1998-2003; 261643 (Box 64, Folder 126)
    - Media Coverage of Trade Missions to Mexico and Africa, 1999-2000; 261644 (Box 64, Folder 127)
    - National Conference of Black Mayors - Dallas, TX, 2000-04; 261645 (Box 64, Folder 128)
    - Democratic National Convention - Los Angeles, 2000-08; 261646 (Box 64, Folder 129)
    - Alpha Phi Alpha Anniversary - Atlanta, GA, 2000-08; 261647 (Box 64, Folder 130)
    - Texas Conference of Black Mayors - Austin, TX, 2000-08; 261648 (Box 64, Folder 131)
    - King Tidell Cottage Foundation - Savannah, GA, 2000-10; 261649 (Box 64, Folder 132)
    - China Aviation Symposium - Washington, DC, 2000-10; 261650 (Box 64, Folder 133)
    - Houston Super Bowl Presentaiton - Atlanta, GA, 2000-10; 261651 (Box 64, Folder 134)
    - ACI Conference - Santago, Chile, 2000-11; 261652 (Box 64, Folder 135)
    - Urban Libraries Council - Chicago, IL, 2000-12; 261653 (Box 64, Folder 136)
    - U.S. Conference of Mayors - Washington, DC, 2001-01; 261654 (Box 64, Folder 137)
    - New York Bond Trip, 2001-02; 261655 (Box 64, Folder 138)
    - City of Houston Legislative Reception - Austin, TX, 2001-02; 261656 (Box 64, Folder 139)
    - Harris County Delegation - Austin, TX, 2001-03; 261657 (Box 64, Folder 140)
    - Greater Houston Partnership Media Trip - New York, Washington, DC, 2001-03; 261658 (Box 64, Folder 141)
    - Texas Conference of Black Mayors - Austin, TX, 2001-03; 261659 (Box 64, Folder 142)
    - Fannie Mae - Washington, DC, 2001-06; 261660 (Box 64, Folder 143)
    - U.S. Conference of Mayors - Detroit, MI, 2001-06; 261661 (Box 64, Folder 144)
    - NAACP Breakfast - New Orleans, LA, 2001-07; 261662 (Box 64, Folder 145)
    - Laredo, TX, 2001-08; 261663 (Box 64, Folder 146)
    - Advisory Commission on Drug Trafficking Problems in Haiti (floppy disk), 2001-12; 261664 (Box 64, Folder 147-148)
    - Advisory Commission on Drug Trafficking Problems in Haiti, 2001-12; 261685 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Conference of Mayors - New York/Washington, DC, 2002-01; 261688 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Super Bowl - San Diego, CA, 2002-01; 261689 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Winter Olympics - Salt Lake City, UT, 2002-02; 261690 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Illinois State University - Chicago, IL, 2002-02; 261692 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - UC Berkeley - Oakland, CA/New York, 2002-02; 261693 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Bond Ratings - New York/Washington, DC, 2002-02; 261694 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - 2012 Roundtable - Washington, DC, 2002-03; 261696 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Ronnie Burns Event - New Orleans, LA, 2002-03; 261697 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Johnny Cochran Event - Los Angeles, CA, 2002-03 - 2002-04; 261701 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Media Tour - New York/Washington, DC, 2002-04; 261702 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - National Forum of Black Public Administrators - Portland, OR, 2002-04; 261703 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Trade Development Mission to Trinidad and Tobago, 2002-04; 261704 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - National Conference of Black Mayors - Jackson, MS, 2002-04; 261705 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Commission on Drug Trafficking - Haiti, 2002-04; 261706 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - CEOs for Cities - Chicago, IL, 2002-05; 261707 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Paul Quinn College - Dallas, TX, 2002-05; 261708 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Howard University Commencement - Washington, DC, 2002-05; 261709 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Business Development Mission to China, 2002-05 - 2002-06; 261711 (Box 65, Folder 19-20)
    - U.S. Conference of Mayors - Madison, WI, 2002-06; 261712 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Washington, DC, 2002-07; 261713 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Albuquerque, NM, 2002-07; 261714 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Trade Development Mission to Mexico, 2002-08; 261715 (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - IAH Retail Concessions - New York, NY, 2002-08; 261716 (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Paul Quinn College Board - Dallas, TX, 2002-09; 261718 (Box 65, Folder 26)
    - Mission to France, 2002-09; 261719 (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Fowler High School 50th Reunion - Fresno, CA, 2002-10; 261721 (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - Trade Mission to the Middle East, 2002-10 - 2002-11; 261725 (Box 65, Folder 29-31)
    - Fresno State University - Fresno, CA, 2002-11; 261727 (Box 65, Folder 32)
    - Paul Quinn College - Dallas, TX, 2003-01; 261728 (Box 65, Folder 33)
    - Wiley College - Marshall, TX, 2003-02; 261729 (Box 65, Folder 34)
    - Transportation Committee Hearings - Austin, TX, 2003-02; 261730 (Box 65, Folder 35)
    - Texas Legislative Reception - Austin, TX, 2003-03; 261731 (Box 65, Folder 36)
    - Official Meetings - New York, NY, 2003-05; 261732 (Box 65, Folder 37)
    - U.S. Conference of Mayors - Denver, CO, 2003-06; 261733 (Box 65, Folder 38)
    - Community Policing Conference - Providence, RI, 2003-06; 261734 (Box 65, Folder 39)
    - Howard University Event - San Antonio, TX, 2003-08; 261736 (Box 65, Folder 40)
    - Trade Mission to Angola and Namibia, 2003-09; 261743 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - NAACP Annual Banquet - Pine Bluff, AK, 2003-11; 261744 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Business Meetings - Washington, DC, 2003-11; 261745 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Business Meetings - New York, NY, 2003-11; 261746 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- Series XII: Post-Mayor Career, 2004-2013, 213483
  - Subseries A: General, 261747
    - 77th Annual Texas State Conference of NAACP Units, 2013; 261749 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - African Cultural Exchange Organization, 2005; 261755 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Alliance for Digital Equality, 2008; 261757 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - American Chamber of Commerce of Jamaica, 2006; 261758 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - American Drug Czars Discuss Drug Policy, 2006; 261760 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Antioch Missionary Baptist Church, 2006; 261765 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - The Berkeley Fellows, 2006-2007; 261766 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Biography/Resume, 2004-2010; 261768 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Bo, Xilia, 2004; 261769 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Book Promotion, 2012; 261771 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Break the Chains, 2007; 261772 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Brown Group International, 2005; 261773 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Chevron, 2005; 261778 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - China Expo, 2005; 261779 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Community Policing Center Proposal, 2004; 261780 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Community Policing in Other Countries, 2004; 261790 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 2004; 261796 (Box 66, Folder 21-24)
    - Correspondence, 2005; 261797 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence, 2006; 261798 (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 2007; 261799 (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 2008; 261800 (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 2009; 261801 (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 2010; 261802 (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, 2011; 261803 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence, 2013; 261804 (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - Cummins, 2005; 261805 (Box 66, Folder 33)
    - Dallas Area Rapid Transit, 2005; 261806 (Box 66, Folder 34)
    - Harvard Institute of Politics, 2005; 261807 (Box 66, Folder 35)
    - Houston Black American Democrats, 2013; 261808 (Box 66, Folder 36)
    - Houston Business and Professional Men's Club Foundation Banquet, 2005; 261809 (Box 66, Folder 37)
    - Houston Community College Black History Month Awards Banquet, 2005; 261810 (Box 66, Folder 38)
    - Houston Forward Times Gala, 2011; 261811 (Box 66, Folder 39)
    - ID Cards, 2008, 2010; 261812 (Box 66, Folder 40)
    - Jackson, Al, 2008; 261813 (Box 66, Folder 41)
    - Lee P. Brown Park - China, 2004; 261814 (Box 66, Folder 42)
    - Locke, Gene, 2004; 261815 (Box 66, Folder 43)
    - Main Street Square, 2004; 261816 (Box 66, Folder 44)
    - Mayoral Administration Accomplishments, 2004; 261817 (Box 66, Folder 45)
    - Museum of Fine Arts Houston Black Artists Catalog, 2004; 261818 (Box 66, Folder 46)
    - News Clippings, 2004; 261819 (Box 66, Folder 47)
    - News Clippings, 2005; 261820 (Box 66, Folder 48)
    - News Clippings, 2006; 261821 (Box 66, Folder 49)
    - News Clippings, 2007; 261822 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - News Clippings, 2008; 261823 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - News Clippings, 2009; 261824 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - News Clippings, 2010; 261825 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - News Clippings, 2011; 261826 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - News Clippings, 2012; 261827 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Notes, 2004; 261828 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Rice University employment, 2003; 261829 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Royal Bahamas Police Force, 2004; 261830 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Sacramento, CA, 2004-2007; 261831 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Sain, Ken, 2005; 261832 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Southern University Law Center Symposium, 2007; 261833 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Southwest Louisiana Partnership, 2005; 261834 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Springarn Medal Nomination, 2008; 261835 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Textbook critique, n.d.; 261836 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - UC Berkeley Charter Banquet Gala, 2005; 261837 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - The United States Conference of Mayors, 2004; 261838 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Unity National Bank, 2005; 261839 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Values, 2004; 261840 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Subseries B: Speeches, 261748
    - Vietnam War Memorial Groundbreaking, 2004; 261841 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Texas Children's Hospital Birthday Gala, 2004-01-09; 261842 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Habifest Luncheon, 2004-03-31; 261843 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - The Justice George Lewis Ruffin Society, 2004-06-23; 261844 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Select Commission on Race and Police Community Relations, 2004-06-27; 261845 (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - National Organization of Black Law Enforcement Executives, 2004-07-12; 261846 (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - Portland State University (floppy disk), 2004; 261847 (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - Payne Cathedral AME Church, ca. 2004; 261848 (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - University of California at Berkeley Gala, 2005-04-16; 261849 (Box 67, Folder 28)
    - National Association for Justice Information Systems, 2005-09-18; 261850 (Box 67, Folder 29)
    - "Homeland Security and Regional Preparedness", ca. 2005; 261851 (Box 67, Folder 30)
    - University of Maryland, ca. 2005; 261852 (Box 67, Folder 31)
    - New Orleans Crime Prevention Summit, 2006-09-16; 261853 (Box 67, Folder 32)
    - Bill Bracey's Funeral, 2006-10-31; 261854 (Box 67, Folder 33)
    - Eliminating Racial Disparities in Substance Abuse Policies, 2006; 261855 (Box 67, Folder 34)
    - New Orleans Rotary Club, 2007-03-14; 261856 (Box 67, Folder 35)
    - "Racial Profiling Prohibited" - North Harris Montgomery Community College, 2007-09-12; 261857 (Box 67, Folder 36)
- Series XIII: Photographs and Drawings, 1945-2004, 213484
  - Subseries A: Photographs, 261873
    - Photographs and negatives, 1945-1957; 261858 (Box 67, Folder 37)
    - Photographs and negatives, 1958-1968; 261859 (Box 67, Folder 38)
    - Photographs - United Nations, ca. 1975; 261860 (Box 67, Folder 39)
    - Photographs and negatives, ca. 1977; 261861 (Box 67, Folder 40)
    - Photographs, ca. 1980; 261862 (Box 67, Folder 41)
    - Photo Album, 1982; 261863 (Box 67, Folder 42)
    - Photographs, 1982; 261864 (Box 67, Folder 43)
    - Marsberg, Germany Scrapbook, 1983; 261865 (Box 67, Folder 44)
    - Photo Album - Trip to Germany, 1982; 261866 (Box 67, Folder 45-46)
    - Photo Album, 1983; 261867 (Box 67, Folder 47)
    - Photographs, 1983; 261868 (Box 67, Folder 48-49)
    - Photo Album, 1984; 261869 (Box 67, Folder 50-51)
    - Photographs, 1984; 261870 (Box 67, Folder 52)
    - Photo Album, 1985; 261871 (Box 67, Folder 53-54)
    - Photographs, 1985; 261872 (Box 67, Folder 55)
    - Photographs, 1986; 261875 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbooks from Mexico Trip, 1986; 261876 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Photographs, ca. 1986; 261879 (Box 68, Folder 3-5)
    - Scrapbook by Tenneco, ca. 1986; 261881 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Photographs, 1987; 261882 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Photo Album, 1988; 261884 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Photographs, 1988 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Photo Album, 1989; 261885 (Box 68, Folder 10-11)
    - Photographs, 1989; 261886 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Photographs, 1990; 261887 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Photographs, 1991; 261888 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Photographs, ca. 1991; 261889 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Photographs, 1992; 261890 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Photographs, 1993; 261891 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Photographs, 1994; 261892 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Photographs, 1996; 261893 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Photographs, 1997; 261894 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Photographs, 1998; 261895 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Photographs, 1999; 261896 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Photographs, ca. 2000; 261897 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Photographs, 2001; 261898 (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Photographs, 2002; 261899 (Box 68, Folder 25)
  - Subseries B: Drawings, 261874
    - ca. 1977, 261900 (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - 1986-1989, 261901 (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - 1997-2004, 261902 (Box 68, Folder 28)
- Series XIV: Video, 1967-2003, 213485
  - Subseries A: Beta/Betacam, 261903
    - 20/20 Atlanta, ca. 1979; 261909 (Box 69)
    - untitled, ca. 1979; 261910 (Box 69)
    - Postscript Commissioner Brown, Educational TV, ca. 1979; 261911 (Box 69)
    - Freeman Reports, aired 05-26, ca. 1979; 261912 (Box 69)
    - The MacNeil/Lehrer Report, 1981-01-08; 261913 (Box 69)
    - The MacNeil/Lehrer Report, "Atlanta", 1981-02-16; 261914 (Box 69)
    - Good Morning America, 1981-02-17; 261915 (Box 69)
    - The Phil Donahue Show, 1981-01-21; 261916 (Box 69)
    - In the Public Interest, 1981-05-31; 261917 (Box 69)
    - Nightline, 1981-07-17; 261918 (Box 69)
    - Dialogue - Atlanta Child Murders, 1981-06-14; 261919 (Box 69)
    - Dick Cavett Show (2 tapes), 1982-01-06; 261922 (Box 69)
    - Nightline, Wayne Williams Conviction (2 tapes), 1982-03-01; 261920 (Box 69)
    - Georgia Speaks, 1982-03-14; 261924 (Box 70)
    - KHOU-TV 11 News Conference, Images, 1982-06-20, 1982-06-27; 261921 (Box 70)
    - "Shoplifting - It's a Crime, Not a Game" - RMA/HISD, Host: Ron Stone, 1982-10; 261925 (Box 70)
    - Viewpoint, 1982-11-30; 261926 (Box 70)
    - Eyewitness Issues and Answers, 1983-01-09; 261927 (Box 70)
    - Pulse with Police Chief Lee Brown, 1983-02-20; 261928 (Box 70)
    - Good Morning in America, Crime in America, Don Kobos "Badge of Two Cities" and John Davenport "Living in Fear", 1983-02; 261929 (Box 70)
    - Good Morning Houston, 1983-03-02; 261930 (Box 70)
    - Ku Klux Klan in Houston, 1983-04-02; 261931 (Box 70)
    - Newscenter interview, 1983-04-20; 261932 (Box 70)
    - Channel 11 Morning Show interview, 1983-05-15; 261933 (Box 70)
    - "Houston Live at Noon" interview, 1983-05-27; 261934 (Box 70)
    - "Thank You, Chief Brown", 1983-06-13; 261935 (Box 70)
    - Houston Police at City Hall news stories, 1983-06-15, 1983-06-16; 261936 (Box 71)
    - "Access to Answer - Crime Prevention", 1983-08-08; 261937 (Box 71)
    - Crossroads and The McNeil/Lehrer Report, 1983-05-10, 1983-05-14; 261938 (Box 71)
    - QUBE "Access to Answers", 1983-08-22; 261939 (Box 71)
    - Fear Reduction Program, 1983-11; 261940 (Box 71)
    - News Addition, 1983-12-12; 261941 (Box 71)
    - KTXH Public Affairs - "A Look to '84", 1983; 261942 (Box 71)
    - The Figgie Report, 1984-01-04; 261943 (Box 71)
    - Use of Firearms Policy (2 tapes), 1984-03-27, 1984-04-18; 261944 (Box 71)
    - Access to Answers interview, 1984-04-09; 261949 (Box 71)
    - KKK March: A Report on Police Activities, 1984-06-09; 261951 (Box 71)
    - FBI National Academy Graduation Exercises, 1984-09-14; 261945 (Box 71)
    - "Houston Live" with Hank Plante and Ginger Casey, 1984-10; 261946 (Box 72)
    - Lee Brown profile (2 tapes), 1984-10-15; 261952 (Box 72)
    - Substation visits, Ku Klux Klan rally and debriefing, anti-KKK demonstration, D.A.R.T., 1984; 261947 (Box 72)
    - Klan tape, 1984; 261948 (Box 72)
    - Atlanta Child Murders TV Mini-Series (6 tapes), 1985; 261953 (Box 72)
    - Blood Donor Drive, ca. 1986; 261954 (Box 72)
    - Fear Reduction, ca. 1986; 261955 (Box 72)
    - Good Morning Houston series on Houston Police Department, ca. 1986; 261956 (Box 72)
    - Houston Police Department Recruiting spot with Lee Brown, ca. 1986; 261957 (Box 72)
    - Law Enforcement, 1988-06-08; 261958 (Box 72)
    - Lee Brown greeting (2 tapes), 1997-10-24; 261959 (Box 72)
  - Subseries B: VHS, 261904
    - Reception Honoring Chief Lee P. Brown and Mrs. Brown, 1982-05-16; 261960 (Box 73)
    - Assorted clips drawn from Beta tapes, 1983; 261961 (Box 73)
    - Chief Brown on Good Morning Houston and Live at Frive, ABC 20/20 Report on Crimestoppers, 1984-08-23; 261962 (Box 73)
    - Atlanta Child Murders - 20/20 News Report, KTRK Channel 13 News, ABC Nightline, 1984-11-08; 261963 (Box 73)
    - Police Commendation, Public Service Awards, Volunteer Graduation, News Interview, 1985-01-07, 1985-01-08, 1985-01-22, 1985-02-14; 261964 (Box 73)
    - KHOU Channel 11 News, Good Morning Houston, "Atlanta Child Murders", 1985-02-07, 1985-02-08, 1985-02-14; 261965 (Box 73)
    - The Atlanta Case on CBS, 1985-02-10, 1985-02-12; 261966 (Box 73)
    - Atlanta Child Murders, Channel 8 News Hour, 1985-02-12; 261967 (Box 73)
    - Atlanta Child Murders, Channel 11, 1985-02-12; 261968 (Box 73)
    - Police Academy Commencement, Promotions, United Way Awards, Interview with Judd McIlvain, 1985-02-22, 1985-03-04, 1985-03-11; 261969 (Box 73)
    - What It Takes Project, 1985-04-02; 261970 (Box 73)
    - Texas Attorney General's Victim's Compensation Program, Operation Child, Promotions, Pro Houston, Commendation Awards, 1985-05-03, 1985-05-10, 1985-06-04, 1985-06-11; 261971 (Box 73)
    - National Black Police Association Judge Alycee Hastings, 1985-08-27; 261972 (Box 73)
    - NBC interview, 1985-08-29; 261973 (Box 73)
    - Ch. 26 documentary "Murder Mystery", 1985-09-03; 261974 (Box 73)
    - Houston Police Department Awards Ceremony - Channel 13, 1985; 261975 (Box 73)
    - The Atlanta Child Murder movie - WAGA TV 5 - After CBS show, 1985; 261976 (Box 73)
    - Atlanta Child Murders, 1985; 261977 (Box 73)
    - Taiwan Provincial Police Academy (2 tapes), 1986-06-10; 261978 (Box 73)
    - B.O.N.D. (Blacks Organizing Neighborhood Defense), ca. 1986; 261979 (Box 73)
    - Chief Brown interview on Channel 26 - "The Black Voice", ca. 1986; 261980 (Box 73)
    - Chief Lee Brown "Traffic Safety", ca. 1986; 261981 (Box 73)
    - The Houston Police Department Presents Graduation of Cadet Class #123, ca. 1986; 261982 (Box 73)
    - The Houston Police Department Presents Graduation of Cadet Class #129, ca. 1986; 261983 (Box 73)
    - HPD: Houston Proud, ca. 1986; 261984 (Box 73)
    - "Houston - We've Got What It Takes", ca. 1986; 261985 (Box 73)
    - Ministers against Crime, ca. 1986; 261986 (Box 73)
    - Neighborhood Oriented Policing, ca. 1986; 261987 (Box 73)
    - Neighborhood Oriented Policing in Houston, Texas, ca. 1986; 261988 (Box 73)
    - New Police Car Press Conference, ca. 1986; 261989 (Box 73)
    - Police Applications of Technology, ca. 1986; 261990 (Box 73)
    - Police Chiefs, ca. 1986; 261991 (Box 73)
    - KHOU Channel 11 - "Spirit of Texas", ca. 1986; 261992 (Box 73)
    - The Margaret Ford Show #108, 1987-01-18; 261993 (Box 73)
    - Summit on Crime in the Black Community (4 tapes), 1987-03-28; 261994 (Box 73)
    - 5 Year Anniversary, 1987; 261995 (Box 73)
    - Neighborhood Oriented Policing (2 tapes), ca. 1987; 261996 (Box 73)
    - "Changing Times" – Black Police Officers, 1988-02-25 (Box 73)
    - Ministers against Crime, 1988-07-01 (Box 73)
    - America's Law Enforcement Response to AIDS, ca. 1988 (Box 73)
    - Leadership Forum, ca. 1988 (Box 73)
    - Profile Lee Brown, ca. 1988 (Box 73)
    - Chief Brown's Journal, 1989-01 (Box 73)
    - Chief Brown's Journal, 1989-02 (Box 74)
    - This Week with David Brinkley, 1989-03-19 (Box 74)
    - Chief Brown's Journal, 1989-03 (Box 74)
    - The McNeil/Lehrer News Hour, 1989-05-16 (Box 74)
    - 1988 Democratic Convention, Channel 2-NBC Drug interview, 1988-07-18 (Box 74)
    - Chief Brown's Journal, 1989-11 (Box 74)
    - Brown interview (3 tapes), 1990-01-05 (Box 74)
    - New Top Cop Commissioner Brown – news excerpts from all channels, 1990-01-05 (Box 74)
    - Swearing in, 1990-01-22 (Box 74)
    - 11th Hour interview, 1990-02-13 (Box 74)
    - "The People's Podium" – Manhattan Cable TV, 1990-02-22 (Box 74)
    - Live at Five interview, 1990-02-23 (Box 74)
    - Social Club Fire—48th Precinct, Mayor Dinkins Live, 1990-03-25, 1990-03-26 (Box 74)
    - Mayor Dinkins Live, 1990-03-26 (Box 74)
    - Democratic National Convention Site Selection Committee Visit to NY (2 tapes), 1990-04-04 – 1990-04-06 (Box 74)
    - Sunday Edition interview, 1990-05-21 (Box 74)
    - Morning Show Channel 2 interview, 1990-07-09 (Box 74)
    - Sunday Edition, Eyewitness News Conference, 1990-08-12 (Box 74)
    - "Community Line" segment – "C-Pop Officers" Manhattan Report with Ruth Messinger, 1990-10-17 (Box 74)
    - Keynote Speaker at Hampshire College's 20th Anniversary Celebration, 1990-10-27 (Box 74)
    - IACP (3 tapes), 1990 (Box 74)
    - NOBLE, 1990 (Box 74)
    - Update for IACP for LETN, 1990 (Box 74)
    - Executive Session on Community Policing (2 tapes), 1991-03-27 (Box 74)
    - Gabe Pressman interview, 1991-04-07 (Box 74)
    - Police Commissioner Update #3: Use of Force, 1991-04-12 (Box 74)
    - Executive Session on Community Policing (2 tapes), 1991-04-17 (Box 74)
    - Positively Black – Law Enforcement, 1991-04-23 (Box 74)
    - Graduation, 1991-04 (Box 74)
    - Lee Brown interview, 1991-04 (Box 74)
    - Executive Session on Community Policing (2 tapes), 1991-05-09 (Box 74)
    - Executive Session on Community Policing (2 tapes), 1991-05-22 (Box 74)
    - Executive Session on Community Policing (2 tapes), 1991-06-12 (Box 74)
    - Training Tape 40 and 25 Precincts, 1991-06-14 (Box 74)
    - City Hall interview, 1991-06-21 (Box 74)
    - Executive Session on Community Policing (2 tapes), 1991-06-26 (Box 74)
    - LETN Excessive Force, 1991-06 (Box 74)
    - Testimony in Washington, DC in regards to Nationwide Community Policing, 1991-07-10 (Box 75)
    - 48 Hours, 1991-07-24 (Box 75)
    - News City, Swearing in: David W. Scott, 1991-08-19 (Box 75)